<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml version="2.0">
	<topic name="Software Development">
    <category>
        <pattern>TELL ME MORE</pattern>
        <template>
            Software Development is a vast field that consists 
            of other subfields. The evergrowning need for software to make our
            lives easier and to support the changes in technology creates the never-ending
            need for new and experienced talent in the Software Development field.
            Computer Programmers are the people who create the code for the software
            that runs the tech world. Two types of
            Computer Programmers are FrontEnd Developers and BackEnd Developers.
            Which career would you like to know more about?
        </template>
    </category>
	<category>
	    <pattern>FRONTEND DEVELOPER</pattern>
	    <template>
	        Front-End Developers work to ensure that company websites are easy 
	        to navigate and aesthetically pleasing for users. In addition to 
	        writing code to create a functional user interface they also implement
	        and adjust visual elements.To learn more about Front-End Developers
	        feel free to ask about the starting pay and skills needed for the job.
	    </template>
    </category>
    <category>
    	<pattern>HOW MUCH DO FRONTEND DEVELOPERS MAKE</pattern>
	    <template>
	        Frontend Developer Median Pay:
	        $73,760 per year
	        
	        Source: ("Web Developers," 2020)
	    </template>
    </category>
    <category>
	    <pattern>WHAT SKILLS DO FRONTEND DEVELOPERS NEED</pattern>
	    <template>
	        According to the BLS Occupational Outlook Handbook, Front-End/Web Developers 
	        "need to have a thorough understanding of HTML programming. Many 
	        employers also want developers to understand other programming 
	        languages, such as JavaScript or SQL, and have knowledge of 
	        multimedia publishing tools, such as Flash" ("Web Developers," 2020).
	    </template>
    </category>
	<category>
	    <pattern>BACKEND DEVELOPER</pattern>
	    <template>
	        Back-End Developers work on code used for the background processes of
	        a website and/or application. They ensure that data from datbases are
	        available for the front-end to work with. To learn more about Back-End Developers
	        feel free to ask about the starting pay and skills needed for the job.
	    </template>
	</category>
	<category>
	    <pattern>HOW MUCH DO BACKEND DEVELOPERS MAKE</pattern>
	    <template>
	        Backend Developer Median Pay:
	        $101,619 per year
	        
	        Source: ("Salary: Backend Developer", 2020)
	    </template>
    </category>
    <category>
	    <pattern>WHAT SKILLS DO BACKEND DEVELOPERS NEED</pattern>
	    <template>
	        According to GeeksforGeeks.org, a popular website for tech infomation, 
	        Backend Developers must be skilled in "manipulating database, different kind of 
	        APIs, the architecture of a system, scripting, etc" (Upadhyay, 2019).
	    </template>
    </category>
    <category>
	    <pattern>HOW MUCH ARE * DEVELOPERS PAID</pattern>
	    <template>
            <srai>HOW MUCH DO <star index="1"/> DEVELOPERS MAKE</srai>
	    </template>
    </category>
    <category>
	    <pattern>WHICH SKILLS ARE NEEDED TO BE A * DEVELOPER</pattern>
	    <template>
            <srai>WHAT SKILLS DO <star index="1"/> DEVELOPERS NEED</srai>
	    </template>
    </category>
    </topic>
    <category>
	    <pattern>I WANT TO LEARN ABOUT OTHER CAREERS</pattern>
	    <template>
	        <think><set name="topic">discover discipline</set></think>
            <srai>YES</srai>
	    </template>
    </category>
</aiml>